Welcome. Today, I'm interviewing Dan Mbanga. , from Amazon AI.
大家好今天我将采访 Dan MbangaDan 来自 Amazon AI 团队
He work on business and technical issues at
他负责解决亚马逊的业务和技术问题
Amazon including things like Amazon's SageMaker.
包括 SageMaker
That's what I want to talk to you today about.
今天我想讨论下 SageMaker
So just to start,
首先
we all have a working definition.
来定义下 SageMaker
How do you describe Amazon SageMaker to someone who's working with machine learning?
你会如何向机器学习人士介绍 Amazon SageMaker？
Yeah. Thank you, Cezanne.
好的谢谢邀请我 Cezanne
Amazon SageMaker is an end-to-end Machine Learning Service.
Amazon SageMaker 是一个端到端机器学习服务
Essentially, it solves the problem of building,
它能够帮助我们构建
training, tuning, and deploying machine learning algorithms.
训练 优化和部署机器学习算法
If you think about our story at Amazon,
对于亚马逊来说
where we do have that by internal and external customers.
我们既有内部客户 又有外部客户
I was at Amazon Web Services.
我之前在 AWS 团队工作
We worked within total Amazon companies.
我们与亚马逊内部公司合作
There are building products for E-commerce or other services like Alexa,
为电子商务或其他服务构建产品 例如 Alexa
there's a lot of machine learning involved there.
我们用到了很多机器学习技术
There are thousands and thousands of data scientists and AI engineers around the world.
世界上有成千上万的数据科学家和 AI 工程师
Building and training machine learning platform that scale.
我们会构建和训练能够扩展的机器学习平台
So we had that challenge of scaling machine learning,
我们需要使机器学习能够扩展
making it accessible to multiple developers,
使多位开发人员能够使用机器学习服务
getting to understand the workflow of machine learning,
还需要了解机器学习的工作流程
and then training people,
然后培训员工
and building tools around
并打造能够为
that workflow to make sure that we ease the process of eventually,
这一流程提供服务的工具 最终使这个流程更轻松
building products with machine learning.
让大家能够使用机器学习构建产品
So gathering that experience,
基于这些经验
we basically decided to create Amazon SageMaker,
我们决定创建 Amazon SageMaker
which essentially follows developers and
它可以从头到尾地
data scientists through the end-to-end process of building,
帮助开发人员和数据科学家
training, and tuning machine learning algorithms.
构建 训练和优化机器学习算法
If you think about that process,
在这个流程中
you have to think about collecting data.
我们需要考虑收集数据
You have to think about an environment where people have to crunch the data,
并且需要考虑一种环境
look at the data distribution, analyze the data,
人们会在此环境下整理数据 查看数据分布 分析数据
and do the whole statistical approach of looking at dataset.
对数据集进行各种统计学分析
That environment needs to be organized in such a way that it has tools that
这个环境必须有条不紊
are enabling these data scientists to essentially get that work done.
能够提供工具 使数据科学家最终能完成工作
The third thing they need to do is to scale
第三个事项是能够扩展这一流程
the process potentially of training these algorithms on large dataset.
以便日后在更大型的数据集上训练这些算法
Then there's a very strong infrastructural orchestration need from
这就需要强大的
that perspective and the other that needs to happen
基础设施规划功能
is figuring out where the models are eventually going to leave.
还需要判断最终将模型部署到哪里
Either in a real application or on a device,
例如部署到实际应用或设备上
and all of these design and orchestration decisions have
以前 数据科学家和开发人员
to traditionally be the responsibility of the scientists and developers.
需要作出所有这些设计和规划决策
SageMaker takes some of that responsibility away,
现在 SageMaker 可以
the undifferentiated heavy lifting essentially and make sure
分担一部分工作
that data scientists and developers can focus on data science,
使数据科学家和开发人员专注于数据科学工作
and the infrastructure and orchestration piece of the work is done by the platform.
基础设施和规划工作将由 SageMaker 平台完成